{
    "id": "4c8a04fc68e6497095399bcdc1dd1219",
    "title": "Less, Lesser, Few, and Fewer",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "871b327d203248539ed23fd8338711f9",
            "title": "Less, Lesser, Few, and Fewer",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "……………… people make their own bread these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Less",
                        "Few",
                        "Lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I earn ....................... money than a sweeper.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "less",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have got ……………….. problems than me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Choose the ………………… of the two evils.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lesser",
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The easiest way to lose weight is to eat …………………. food.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ……………….. friends than her sister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fewer",
                        "less",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to spend ……………… of my time cooking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lesser",
                        "fewer",
                        "less"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I worry …………………. than I used to.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fewer",
                        "less",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There were ………………… of us at the college reunion.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fewer",
                        "less",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The script was written by a …………………. known writer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "lesser",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We did ....................... work today than yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lesser",
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The baby is ................................ ugly than you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "lesser",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}